<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Donate</string>
    <string name="story">
        "Welcome to my donation application!"

        "\n\nMy name is Amir Zaidi and I am a student at Delft, University of Technology, in the Netherlands."
        "I hope you have been enjoying the Android applications I have made."
        "Everything I do is open source so others can continue my work, and make even better apps."
        "All of this is free for both users and developers."

        "\n\nProgramming has always been a hobby of me, ever since primary school."
        "Throughout the years I have learned many different skills."
        "I started on websites, then moved to Windows applications, and am now doing Android development."

        "\n\nHere is a list of my Android-related projects"
        "\n- Global Squeeze"
        "\n- Rootless Pixel Launcher"
        "\n- Rootless Pixel Bridge"
        "\n- Google Icons"
        "\n- Material FX"
        "\n- Adaptive Stune"
        "\n- Dynamica Live Wallpaper"
        "\n- DNG Processor"
        "\n- Night Camera"
        "\n- Ozone Essentials"
        "\n- Audio Streamer"
        "\n- Assist Mapper"

        "\n\nNow I, as everyone else, have only a limited amount of time."
        "Still, I feel like there aren't enough open source developments and want to push other developers to adopt the model too, so I keep going."
        "You can support me and my journey by donating with the orange button above."
        "Every gift will be remembered, and put to use for updates and new applications in the future."

        "\n\nIf you wish to contact me, it is very easy to reach me outside of school hours."
        "Click on the three dots in the top right corner of the screen."
        "There you can select either Telegram or E-mail as the means to reach me."
        "I do not read my e-mails often, so if you have something urgent I recommend using Telegram."

        "\n\nThanks for reading my story!"
        "\nAmir Zaidi"
    </string>

    <string name="action_telegram">Telegram</string>
    <string name="action_mail">E-Mail</string>

    <string name="donate_title">Support me</string>
    <string name="donate_desc">Here you can send me a donation if you want to.</string>
    <string name="donate_new">Thank you for your support! &lt;3</string>
    <string name="donate_history">Thank you for your support!</string>
</resources>
