<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Support</string>
    <string name="story">
        "Hey!"

        "\n\nMy name is Amir and I am a student at Delft, University of Technology, in the Netherlands."
        "I hope you've been enjoying the Android applications I work on!"

        "\n\nProgramming has always been a hobby of me, ever since primary school."
        "Throughout the years I have learned many different skills."
        "I started on websites, then moved to PC programs, and am now doing Android development."

        "\n\nThe Android apps I'm proud of are DNGP, Shade, RPL and Pixel Bridge."
        "But there are many more apps that I've worked on, and you've probably never heard of them."
        "For example, I recreated the Squeeze for Assistant feature on other phones, without pressure sensors."
        "There's Google Icons, Material FX, Adaptive Stune, Dynamica, Ozone Essentials, Audio Streamer, Assist Mapper, and many more small projects on my GitHub."

        "\n\nEverything I do is free and open source so others can improve it and make even better apps."
        "Now I, as everyone else, have only a limited amount of time."
        "Still I feel like there isn't enough open source development and want to push other developers to adopt the model too."
        "You can support me and my journey by buying A Feeling of Pride and Accomplishment with the orange button above."
        "When you have bought it you will unlock a banner in the app that thanks you for the purchase."
        "Every purchase will be remembered, and put to use for updates and new applications in the future."

        "\n\nIf you wish to contact me, it is easy to reach me outside of school hours."
        "Click on the three dots in the top right corner of the screen."
        "There you can select either Telegram or E-mail as the means to reach me."
        "I do not read my e-mails often, so if you have something urgent I highly recommend using Telegram."

        "\n\nThanks for reading my story!"
        "\n\nAmir Zaidi"
    </string>

    <string name="action_telegram">Telegram</string>
    <string name="action_mail">E-Mail</string>

    <string name="donate_new">Thank you for buying A Feeling of Pride and Accomplishment!</string>
    <string name="donate_history">Enjoy your feeling of pride and accomplishment!</string>
</resources>
